{
	"Welcome": [
        {
            "question": "This website has a bunch of groups with questions.  Pick a group, answer some questions and then check out a profile to see your rating.",
            "rightAnswer": "This is the right answer",
            "wrongAnswer": "This is the wrong answer"
        }
    ],
    "Java Beginner Questions": [
        {
            "question": "Which one of these is a java IDE",
            "rightAnswer": "Eclipse",
            "wrongAnswer": "Visual Studio"
        },
        {
            "question": "What makes an IDE useful",
            "rightAnswer": "It allows for code completion",
            "wrongAnswer": "It allows for the editing of files"
        },
        {
            "question": "The difference between an abstract class and an interface is the ability to call an interface from any method",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        },
        {
            "question": "Object orientation in Java allows for more abstraction",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "StringBuffers are immutable in Java",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "Strings are immutable in Java",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        }
    ],
    "Java Advanced Questions": [
        {
            "question": "If there are two places where you have compiled the same static string, can you use the == method across the two different variables?",
            "rightAnswer": "Yes",
            "wrongAnswer": "No"
        },
        {
            "question": "In Java 8 taking a small part of a string using the substring method can cause a memory leak",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        }
    ],
    "HTML Basic Questions": [
        {
            "question": "The <table> tag should be used to represent layout",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        },
        {
            "question": "CSS should be used to represent layout",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        },
        {
            "question": "The h1 element should represent the heading of the page",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "The p element represents pronouns",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "The a element represents links",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "The a element represents links",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "Href is a part of the p element",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        },
        {
            "question": "Src is a part of the img element",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "The img element shows images on a page",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "The li element limits the amount of items on a page",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        },
        {
            "question": "The li element shows lists on a page",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ui element holds li elements",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        },
        {
            "question": "The ui element holds a elements",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        }
    ],
    "HTML Advanced Questions": [
        {
            "question": "The a element is an anchor",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        }
    ],
    "Software Development Basic Questions": [
        {
            "question": "Array indexing should start with",
            "rightAnswer": "0",
            "wrongAnswer": "1"
        }
    ],
    "SQL Basic Questions": [
        {
            "question": "Getting data is accomplished with the GET keyword",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        }
    ],
    
    "programming basic Questions": [
        {
            "question": "In programming for is used to format code",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        }
    ],
    
    "python basic questions": [
        {
            "question": "friends = new String['john', 'pat', 'gary', 'michael'] will set an array",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        },
        {
            "question": "def greet(name):\n    print 'Hello', name \n Will define a function",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        },
        
        {
            "question": "prices = {'apple': 0.40, 'banana': 0.50}\n Will define a dictionary",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "def greet(name):\n    print 'Hello', name \n Will define a function",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "friends = ['john', 'pat', 'gary', 'michael'] will set an array",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "name = raw_input('What is your name?\n') will take text from the console",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        },
        {
            "question": "print 'Hello, world!' will send text to the console",
            "rightAnswer": "Correct",
            "wrongAnswer": "Incorrect"
        }
        
        

    ]

    "python intermediate questions": [
        {
            "question": "print 'Hello World'[3]\n throws an error",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        },
        {
            "question": "print 'Hello World'[-3]\n throws an error",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        },
        {
            "question": "print 'Hello World'[3]\n returns l",
            "rightAnswer": "Incorrect",
            "wrongAnswer": "Correct"
        }
    ]
}